

CONTACT

- +010-2798-1527
- ☑ jongsooy0127@gmail.com
- Yongin, South Korea
- Github
- 💄 🛮 F4 Visa

SKILLS

- HTML5 / CSS3
- Javascript ES6
- O Python
- SQL
- Github
- API
- MariaDB
- React (In progress)

LANGUAGES

- English (Native)
- Korean (Advanced)

EDUCATION

March 2024-Present

WCODING, SEOUL Full Stack Web Development

2012-2016

UNIVERSITY AT BUFFALO, NY Management Information System

JONG SOO YOON

Full Stack Developer

PERSONAL PROFILE

Motivated entry level web developer with experience in creating websites, testing, and debugging code. 5 years of experience in education and 2 years of experience in conflict resolution. Seeking permanent role in front end or back end web development in South Korea. I am hoping to use my Javascript and Python skill to add value to your company's needs.

IT PROJECTS

HOGA Github

- Lead backend engineer and role is to create, maintain, and debug the backend code utilizing Flask, Python, SQL, and MariaDB
- Utilize OpenWeatherMap and Google Gemini API services to create widgets for users to interact with
- Oversee the structure of the database, and organize the data going into the database
- Experience in working in a team environment, and contributing to the objectives and goals of our team's project
- Employ Github to collaborate with team members

TIC - TAC - TOE Github | Demo

HTML5, CSS3, and Javascript to create a tic-tac-toe game

• UNIVERSITY SEARCH Github

- HTML5, CSS3, and Javascript to create a search application for universities in the United States
- Employed API to gather data of universities in the United States

WORK EXPERIENCE

ENGLISH TEACHER | 2018-2024

DYB | Sungmin Kindergarten | BPA

- Provided easy to understand directions to keep students engaged with lessons.
- Demonstrated time management skill when creating lessons according to deadlines.

CUSTOMER SERVICE REPRESENTATIVE | 2016-2018

delivery.com | Spectrum

- Displayed attention to detail when updating customer's account.
- Communicated via email or telephone to resolve conflicts.
- Collaborated in a team to resolve complications that were encountered after the acquisition of Time Warner
- Demonstrated problem solving skill through troubleshooting customer's set top boxes